{
    "subject": "resource/Kelly_Johnson_(engineer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ishpeming,_Michigan",
    "human_readable": "Kelly Johnson (engineer) was born in Ishpeming, Michigan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9309462904930115,
            "question": "Is Kelly Johnson an engineer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8230810761451721,
            "question": "Where was Kelly Johnson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229279518127441,
            "question": "Name the city where Kelly Johnson was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908299565315247,
            "question": "In which state was Kelly Johnson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6022059917449951,
            "question": "What profession is Kelly Johnson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49470338225364685,
            "question": "What is Kelly Johnson's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46994897723197937,
            "question": "Where did Kelly Johnson likely grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1945861130952835,
            "question": "Can you name some famous engineers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13822124898433685,
            "question": "What makes a successful engineer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05813920870423317,
            "question": "What are some important contributions of engineers to society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kelly Johnson (engineer) was born in Ishpeming, Michigan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2757_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a successful engineer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2757_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some famous engineers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2757_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Kelly Johnson likely grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2757_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2757_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Kelly Johnson (engineer) was born in Ishpeming, Michigan.\" Multiple sources confirm his birthplace as Ishpeming, Michigan, and describe him as an aircraft engineer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}